<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.p2p-streams"
       name="p2p-streams"
       version="1.2.0"
       provider-name="enen92,fightnight">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
    <import addon="script.module.pytz" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.mechanize" version="0.2.6"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>SopCast and AceStream</summary>
    <description lang="en">AceStream and Sopcast in your favourite media center! Watch peer-to-peer streams in Kodi without the need for external players. Project page: https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi</description>
    <description lang="pt">AceStream e Sopcast no seu Media-Center de eleição! Assista a streams peer-to-peer no Kodi sem a necessidade de players externos. Página do projecto: https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi</description>
    <description lang="nl">Acestream en Sopcast in jouw favoriete media center. Kijk peer-to-peer streams in Kodi zonder de noodzaak voor externe spelers. Project pagina: https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi/</description>
    <description lang="it">AceStream e SopCast nel tuo Media Center preferito! Guarda i canali peer-to-peer in Kodi senza la necessità di player esterni. Pagina del progetto: https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi/</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en">The authors does not host nor distribute any of the content you may watch using this addon. The authors have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon does not track its users.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Os autores não alojam nem distribuem nenhum do conteúdo acessível a partir deste addon. Os autores não têm qualquer afiliação com nenhum dos sites utilizados por este addon. O addon não contem nenhuma ferramenta de tracking.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">De auteurs houden of delen niets van de inhoud die u kunt bekijken met behulp van deze addon. De auteurs hebben geen banden met welke leverancier van inhoud dan ook. Deze addon houdt geen gegevens bij van zijn gebruikers.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">L'autore non detiene o distribuisce alcun contenuto fruibile tramite l'utilizzo di questo addon. L'autore non è affiliato con nessun fornitore dei contenuti. Questo addon non traccia i suoi utenti.</disclaimer>
    <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=201894</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi | https://github.com/enen92/P2P-Streams-Kodi--Modules-</source>
    <website>https://code.google.com/p/p2p-strm/</website>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
